<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addons>

<addon id="script.artistslideshow" name="Artist Slideshow" provider-name="pkscout,ronie" version="3.2.1">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.26.0" />
		<import addon="xbmc.addon" version="17.9.0" />
		<import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.3.0" />
		<import addon="script.module.defusedxml" version="0.6.0" />
		<import addon="script.module.kodi-six" version="0.0.3" />
		<import addon="script.module.future" version="0.16.0.4" />
	</requires>
	<extension library="default.py" point="xbmc.python.script">
		<provides>executable</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<news>
v.3.2.1
- added option to pause slideshow when playback pauses
- logic change to load first slideshow image sooner
- override slideshow no longer resets at each song change
- fix for potential runaway loop
- fix for slow slideshow change when artist changes
- fix for AS not reloading settings properly when in daemon mode
- fixes for miscellaneous UTF8 errors
- internal change to the way the main thread talks to the slideshow thread
		</news>
		<assets>
        	<icon>icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
		<summary lang="ar_SA">حمل المزيد من الصور والمعلومات عن الفنان الذى يُغنِى حالياً</summary>
		<summary lang="be_BY">Download images and additional info of the currently playing artist</summary>
		<summary lang="bg_BG">Сваля изображения и допълнителна инф. за изпълнителя на текущата песен</summary>
		<summary lang="ca_ES">Descàrrega imatges i informació addicional de l'artista que s'està reproduint</summary>
		<summary lang="da_DK">Download billeder og ekstra info om kunstneren, der spiller i øjeblikket</summary>
		<summary lang="de_DE">Downloade Bilder und zusätzliche Informationen des aktuellen abspielenden Künstlers.</summary>
		<summary lang="el_GR">Κατεβάστε εικόνες και επιπλέον πληροφορίες του τρέχοντος καλλιτέχνη</summary>
		<summary lang="en_GB">Download images and additional info of the currently playing artist</summary>
		<summary lang="en_NZ">Download images and additional info of the currently playing artist</summary>
		<summary lang="en_US">Download images and additional info of the currently playing artist</summary>
		<summary lang="es_ES">Descarga imágenes e información adicional del artista que esté sonando</summary>
		<summary lang="es_AR">Bajá imágenes e información adicional sobre el artista </summary>
		<summary lang="fr_FR">Télécharger les images et les informations additionnelles de l'artiste en cours de lecture</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_CA">Télécharger des images et des infos additionnelles sur l'artiste écouté</summary>
		<summary lang="gl_ES">Descarga imaxes e info. adicional do artista que está a soar</summary>
		<summary lang="he_IL">הורד תמונות ומידע נוסף על האמן המושמע כעת</summary>
		<summary lang="hr_HR">Preuzimite slike i dodatne informacije o trenutno reproduciranom izvođaču</summary>
		<summary lang="hu_HU">Képeket és kiegészítő információkat tölt le a jelenleg játszott előadóról</summary>
		<summary lang="it_IT">Scarica immagini ed informazioni addizionali dell'artista attualmente in esecuzione</summary>
		<summary lang="ja_JP">現在再生中のアーティストの画像と追加情報をダウンロードする</summary>
		<summary lang="ko_KR">현재 재생중인 아티스트의 이미지와 추가 정보 다운로드</summary>
		<summary lang="nl_NL">Downloaden van afbeeldingen en extra informatie van te horen artiest</summary>
		<summary lang="nb_NO">Last ned bilder og ytterligere informasjon om artisten som spilles av</summary>
		<summary lang="pl_PL">Pobieraj obrazy i dodatkowe informacje o aktualnie odtwarzanym wykonawcy</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_PT">Transferir imagens e info adicional do artista em reprodução agora</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">Transferência de imagens e informações adicionais de artistas que estejam sendo reproduzidos</summary>
		<summary lang="ru_RU">Загрузить фото и дополнительную информацию об воспроизводимом исполнителе</summary>
		<summary lang="sk_SK">Stiahnuť obrázky a dodatočné informácie o práve hrajúcich interpretoch</summary>
		<summary lang="sl_SI">Naložite slike in dodatne informacije, za trenutno predvajanega izvajalca</summary>
		<summary lang="sv_SE">Ladda ner bilder samt ytterligare information om den spelade artisten</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_CN">下载当前播放艺人的图片和附加信息</summary>
		<description lang="ar_SA">ملحق يساعدك على تَنِزِيل صور ومعلومات إضافيه عن الفنان الذى تستمع اليه حالياً من موقع fanart.tv و theaudiodb.com. كما يمكنك جعل جلد واجهتك الحالى يستخدم كل ما سبق ﻹنشاء عروض شرائح للفنان الذى تستمع إليه</description>
		<description lang="bg_BG">Добавката сваля картинки и допълнителна информация от www.fanart.tv и www.theaudiodb.com за изпълнителя който звучи в момента. Картинките, заедно с фанарт изображенията на изпълнителя, може да се ползват от облика, за създаването на слайдшоу за изпълнителя, който звучи в момента.</description>
		<description lang="ca_ES">Complement per descarregar imatges i informació addicional de fanart.tv i theaudiodb.com de l'artista que s'està reproduint. Les imatges, juntament amb les imatges locals d'artistes, i la informació, pot ser utilitzada per la pell per crear una presentació de diapositives per a l'artista que s'està escoltant.</description>
		<description lang="de_DE">Addon um Bilder und zusätzliche Informationen von fanart.tv und theaudiodb.com zum aktuell gespielten Künstler herunterzuladen. Diese Bilder können zusammen mit den lokalen Künstlerbildern und Infos vom Skin genutzt werden, um eine Slideshow für den aktuell angehörten Künstler zu erstellen.</description>
		<description lang="el_GR">Πρόσθετο για τη λήψη εικόνων και επιπλέον πληροφοριών από το fanart.tv  και το theaudiodb.com για τον τρέχοντα καλλιτέχνη. Οι εικόνες, μαζί με τοπικές εικόνες του καλλιτέχνη καθώς και πληροφορίες, μπορούν να χρησιμοποιηθούν από το κέλυφος για τη δημιουργία παρουσιάσεων διαφανειών του καλλιτέχνη η μουσική του οποίου ακούγεται.</description>
		<description lang="en_GB">Addon to download images and additional information from fanart.tv and theaudiodb.com of the currently playing artist. The images, along with local artists' images, and info can be used by the skin to create a slideshow for the artist being listened to.</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">Addon to download images and additional information from fanart.tv and theaudiodb.com of the currently playing artist. The images, along with local artists' images, and info can be used by the skin to create a slideshow for the artist being listened to.</description>
		<description lang="en_US">Addon to download images and additional information from fanart.tv and theaudiodb.com of the currently playing artist. The images, along with local artists' images, and info can be used by the skin to create a slideshow for the artist being listened to.</description>
		<description lang="es_ES">Addon para descargar imágenes e información adicional de fanart.tv y theaudiodb.com del artista que se está reproduciendo. Las imágenes, junto con imágenes de artistas locales, y la información puede ser utilizada por la piel para crear una presentación de diapositivas para el artista que se está escuchando.</description>
		<description lang="fr_CA">Addiciel pour télécharger des images et des informations additionnelles sur fanart.tv et theaudiodb.com de l'artiste en cours d'écoute. Les images, ainsi que les images locales de l'artiste, et les infos peuvent être utilisées par l'habillage pour créer un diaporama pour l'artiste en cours d'écoute.</description>
		<description lang="gl_ES">Complemento para descargar imaxes e información adicional de fanart.tv e theaudiodb.com do artista que está a soar. Estas imaxes, xunto cas do artista gardadas en local e a información pódeas usar o tema para crear unha presentación. </description>
		<description lang="he_IL">הרחבה להורדת תמונות ומידע נוסף על האמן המושמע כעת מ-fanart.tv ו- theaudiodb.com. התמונות, בנוסף לתמונות אמנים מקומיות והמידע על אמן יכולים לשמש את המעטפת ליצירת מצגת עבור האמן המושמע כעת.</description>
		<description lang="hr_HR">Dodatak za preuzimanje slika i dodatnih informacije trenutno reproduciranog izvođača s fanart.tv, theaudiodb.com i theaudiodb.com. Slike, zajedno s lokalnim slikama izvođača i informacijama mogu se koristiti s presvlakom za stvaranje slikovne prezentacije izvođača koji se sluša.</description>
		<description lang="hu_HU">A Kiegészítő letölt képeket és infromációkat a fanart.tv és theaudiodb.com oldalakról az éppen hallgatott előadóhoz. A képek a helyben tárolt képekkel együtt felhasználhatóak a Felszín által diavetítéshez.</description>
		<description lang="it_IT">Addon per scaricare immagini ed informazioni aggiuntive da fanart.tv e theaudiodb.com sull'artista attualmente in esecuzione. Le immagini possono essere usate dallo skin, insieme a quelle locali, per creare una presentazione  per l'artista che si sta ascoltando.</description>
		<description lang="ko_KR">현재 재생중인 아티스트의 이미지와 추가정보를 fanart.tv 와 theaudiodb.com 에서 다운로드합니다. 다운로드한 이미지와 정보는 로컬 이미지와 함께 현재 재생중인 음악의 아티스트 슬라이드쇼에 사용할 수 있습니다.</description>
		<description lang="nl_NL">Add-on om afbeeldingen en bijkomende informatie van Fanart.tv en theaudiodb.com van de te horen artiest binnen te halen. de afbeeldingen, net als de lokaal aanwezige artiest-afbeeldingen en -info kunnen gebruikt worden door de skin om een diashow te tonen van de artiest di nu beluisterd wordt.</description>
		<description lang="nb_NO">Tillegg for å laste ned bilder og ytterligere informasjon fra fanart.tv og theaudiodb.com for artisten som spilles av for øyeblikket. Bildene, sammen med lokale artistbilder og info, kan bli brukt av skallet til å lage en lysbildefremvisning for artisten som blir lyttet til for øyeblikket.</description>
		<description lang="pl_PL">Wtyczka pobiera obrazy i dodatkowe informacje z fanart.tv oraz theaudiodb.com o aktualnie odtwarzanym wykonawcy. Obrazami wraz z informacjami o wykonawcach, mogą być wykorzystywane przez skórę do tworzenia pokazu slajdów dla artysty, którego aktualnie słuchasz.</description>
		<description lang="pt_PT">Um add-on para transferir imagens e informação adicional do artista em reprodução no momento, a partir de fanart.tv e theaudiodb.com. As imagens e a informação, assim como as imagens locais dos artistas, podem ser usadas pelo tema para criar uma apresentação de slides do artista em escuta no momento.</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Addon para download de imagens e informações adicionais do artista que está sendo reproduzido provido por fanart.tv e theaudiodb.  Tais dados e imagens serão usados pelas skins para criarem um slideshow dos artistas quando estivermos escutando-os.</description>
		<description lang="ru_RU">Дополнение для загрузки изображений и дополнительной информации о воспроизводимом исполнителе с ресурсов fanart.tv and theaudiodb.com. Загруженные изображения и доп. информация, наравне с локальными, могут быть использованы для создания слайд-шоу во время прослушивания композиций.</description>
		<description lang="sl_SI">Dodatek za prenos slik in dodatnih informacij  iz fanart.tv in theaudiodb.com za trenutno predvajanega izvajalca. Slike, skupaj z lokalnimi slikami izvajalcev ter informacije, se lahko uporabljajo s preobleko za ustvarjanje diaprojekcije slik izvajalca, ki ga trenutno poslušate.</description>
		<description lang="sv_SE">Tillägg för att ladda ner bilder och tilläggsinformation från fanart.tv och theaudiodb.com om artisten som spelas för tillfället. Bilderna, tillsammans med lokala artistbilder och information, kan användas av skinnet för att skapa ett bildspel av artisten man lyssnar på.</description>
		<description lang="zh_CN">从fanart.tv和theaudiodb.com下载当前播放艺人的图片和附加信息的插件。这此图片可以和本地艺人图片及信息一起，被皮肤用来创建正收听的艺人的幻灯片。</description>
		<language />
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
		<forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?t=124880</forum>
		<website>https://kodi.wiki/index.php?title=Add-on:Artist_Slideshow</website>
		<email>artistslideshow.xbmc@gmail.com</email>
		<source>https://github.com/pkscout/script.artistslideshow</source>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.speedfaninfo" name="SpeedFan Information Display" version="1.1.0" provider-name="pkscout">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0" />
		<import addon="xbmc.addon" version="17.0.0" />
		<import addon="script.module.kodi-six" version="0.0.3" />
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py">
		<provides>executable</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<news>
v.1.1.0
- SpeedFan Information Display no longer uses python threads to accomplish window updates
- moved common libs to lib folder and eliminated unused common libraries
- changed XBMC to Kodi in addon description
		</news>
		<summary lang="af">Vertoon inligting van jou SpeedFan Aantekenings.</summary>
		<summary lang="be">Display information from your SpeedFan log.</summary>
		<summary lang="bg">Показва информация от вашия SpeedFan дневник.</summary>
		<summary lang="ca">Mostra la informació del Registre de Velocitats del Ventilador.</summary>
		<summary lang="da">Vis oplysninger fra din SpeedFan-log.</summary>
		<summary lang="de">Zeige Informationen aus deinem SpeedFan Log.</summary>
		<summary lang="el">Προβολή πληροφοριών από το αρχείο καταγραφής του SpeedFan.</summary>
		<summary lang="en">Display information from your SpeedFan log.</summary>
		<summary lang="en_NZ">Display information from your SpeedFan log.</summary>
		<summary lang="en_US">Display information from your SpeedFan log.</summary>
		<summary lang="es">Muestra información del log de SpeedFan</summary>
		<summary lang="es_MX">Muestra información desde tu log de SpeedFan</summary>
		<summary lang="et">Kuvab info SpeedFan logist.</summary>
		<summary lang="fr">Afficher les informations à partir du journal de SpeedFan</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_CA">Afficher l'information du journal pour SpeedFan</summary>
		<summary lang="gl">Amosar información do teu rexistro de SpeedFan.</summary>
		<summary lang="he">הצג מידע מיומן הרישום של SpeedFan.</summary>
		<summary lang="hr">Prikaz informacija iz vašeg SpeedFan zapisa.</summary>
		<summary lang="hu">Ventilátor-sebesség napló megjelenítése</summary>
		<summary lang="id">Menampilkan informasi log SpeedFan Anda.</summary>
		<summary lang="it">Mostra le informazioni dal tuo log di SpeedFan</summary>
		<summary lang="nl">Laat informatie zien van het SpeedFan log</summary>
		<summary lang="pl">Wyświetla infromacje z dziennika SpeedFan</summary>
		<summary lang="pt">Exibe informação do seu log do Speedfan.</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">Mostrar informações de seu registro SpeedFan.</summary>
		<summary lang="ru">Отображает информацию из Вашего журнала SpeedFan.</summary>
		<summary lang="sk">Zobraziť informácie z Vášho SpeedFan logu.</summary>
		<summary lang="sv">Visar information från din SpeedFan logg.</summary>
		<summary lang="zh">显示来源于SpeedFan日志的信息</summary>
		<description lang="af">Ontleed en vertoon inligting van die SpeedFan Aantekenings. Terwyl hierdie plugin werk op enige platform, SpeedFan werk net op Windows, so dit is optimaal gebou vir mense wat Kodi op Windows gebruik. Sien readme.txt vir inligting oor hoe om jou SpeedFan Aantekenings in te stel sodat die prop dit behoorlik kan ontleed nie.</description>
		<description lang="be">Parses and displays information from the SpeedFan log. While this plugin works on any platform, SpeedFan only works on Windows, so it is optimally built for people using Kodi on Windows. Please see readme.txt for information on how to configure your SpeedFan log so that the plugin can parse it properly.</description>
		<description lang="bg">Извлича и показва информацията от дневника на SpeedFan. Приставката работи на всички платформи, но самият SpeedFan работи само на Windows, така че приставката е особено полезна за потребителите ползващи Kodi на Windows. Моля, прочетете readme.txt файла за да получите допълнителна информация, за това как как да конфигурирате вашия SpeedFan дневник, така че приставката да може да го анализира правилно</description>
		<description lang="ca">Analitza i mostra la informació del Registre de Velocitats del Ventilador. Encara que aquest plugin sigui multiplataforma, el Registre de Velocitats del Ventilador només funciona sobre Windows, de manera que està construït òptimament per les persones que utilitzen Kodi sobre Windows. Si et plau, llegeix el fitxer readme.txt per a més informació sobre com configurar el teu Registre de Velocitats del Ventilador i permetre al plugin analitzar els valors correctament.</description>
		<description lang="da">Henter og viser information fra SpeedFan log'en. Selvom dette plugin virker på alle platforme, fungerer SpeedFan kun i Windows og er dermed skabt for folk, som kører Kodi på Windows. Se venligst readme.txt for oplysninger om, hvordan du opsætter din SpeedFan log, så plugin'et kan læse den korrekt.</description>
		<description lang="de">Analysiert und zeigt Informationen vom SpeedFan log. Während dieses Plugin auf allen Plattformen funktioniert, läuft SpeedFan nur unter Windows, also ist es optimal für, die, die Kodi unter Windows nutzen. Bitte ließ die readme.txt für Informationen, wie SpeedFan konfiguriert werden muss, dass das Plugin den Log korrekt analysieren kann.</description>
		<description lang="el">Αναλύει και προβάλλει πληροφορίες από το αρχείο καταγραφής του SpeedFan. Ενώ αυτό το plugin δουλεύει σε οποιαδήποτε πλατφόρμα, το SpeedFan δουλεύει μόνο σε Windows, συνεπώς είναι φτιαγμένο για ανθρώπους που χρησιμοποιούν το Kodi σε Windows. Δείτε το readme.txt για πληροφορίες σχετικά με τη ρύθμιση του αρχείου καταγραφής του SpeedFan ούτως ώστε το plugin να μπορέσει να το αναλύσει σωστά.</description>
		<description lang="en">Parses and displays information from the SpeedFan log. While this plugin works on any platform, SpeedFan only works on Windows, so it is optimally built for people using Kodi on Windows. Please see readme.txt for information on how to configure your SpeedFan log so that the plugin can parse it properly.</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">Parses and displays information from the SpeedFan log. While this plugin works on any platform, SpeedFan only works on Windows, so it is optimally built for people using Kodi on Windows. Please see readme.txt for information on how to configure your SpeedFan log so that the plugin can parse it properly.</description>
		<description lang="en_US">Parses and displays information from the SpeedFan log. While this plugin works on any platform, SpeedFan only works on Windows, so it is optimally built for people using Kodi on Windows. Please see readme.txt for information on how to configure your SpeedFan log so that the plugin can parse it properly.</description>
		<description lang="es">Analiza y muestra información del log de SpeedFan. Aunque este complemento funciona en cualquier plataforma, Speedfan sólo funciona en Windows, por lo que está optimizado para el público que utiliza Kodi en Windows. Por favor, lea el fichero readme.txt para obtener información de cómo configurar el log de SpeedFan, de forma que el complemento la interprete correctamente.</description>
		<description lang="es_MX">Parsea y muestra información desde el log de SpeedFan. Mientras este plugin funciona en cualquier plataforma, SpeedFan funciona solamente en Windows, así que está construido de manera óptima para personas que usan Kodi en Windows. Para información en como configurar el log de SpeedFan para que el plugin pueda parsearlo de manera adecuada, revisar readme.txt.</description>
		<description lang="et">Kogub ja kuvab info SpeedFan logist. Kuigi plugin töötab kõigil platvormidel, siis SpeedFan töötab vaid Windowsis, nii et vajalik on ta vaid neile, kes kasutavad Kodi-d Windows platvormil. SpeedFan logi seadistamine nii, et seda plugin suudaks veavabalt töödelda, on kirjas failis readme.txt.</description>
		<description lang="fr">Analyse et affiche les informations à partir du journal de SpeedFan. Même si ce module fonctionne sur toutes les plateformes, SpeedFan ne fonctionne que sous Windows, il est donc optimisé pour les utilisateurs de Kodi sous Windows. Merci de lire le fichier readme.txt pour savoir comment configurer votre journal SpeedFan afin que le module puisse l'analyser correctement.</description>
		<description lang="fr_CA">Analyse et affiche les informations du journal SpeedFan. Bien que cette extension fonctionne sur n'importe quelle plateforme, SpeedFan ne fonctionne que sur Windows, il est parfaitement construit pour les personnes utilisant Kodi sur Windows. S'il vous plaît voir le fichier readme.txt pour plus d'informations sur la façon de configurer votre journal SpeedFan pour que le module d'extension puisse l'analyser correctement.</description>
		<description lang="gl">Ananilza e amosa información do rexistro de SpeedFan. Mentres que este engadido funciona en calquera plataforma, SpeedFan só funciona baixo Windows polo que está optimizado para o Kodi de Windows. Por favor lea readme.txt para obter información de como configurar o rexistro de SpeedFan para que o engadido o poda analizar dunha forma axeitada.</description>
		<description lang="he">מנתחת ומציגה מידע מיומן הרישום של SpeedFan. אמנם הרחבה זו תרוץ על כל פלטפורמה אך SpeedFan רצה רק על מערכת חלונות, לכן הרחבה זו מתאימה במיוחד למשתמשי Kodi תחת חלונות. אנא ראה readme.txt למידע בנושא הגדרת יומן הרישום של SpeedFan כך שההרחבה תנתח את המידע נכונה.</description>
		<description lang="hr">Analizira i prikazuje informacije iz SpeedFan zapisa. dok ovaj dodatak radi na bilo kojoj platformi, SpeedFan radi na Windowsima, stoga je optimalno izgrađen za ljude koji koriste Kodi na Windowsima. Pogledajte readme.txt za više informacija o podešavanju vašeg SpeedFan zapisa zato da ga dodatak može ispravno analizirati.</description>
		<description lang="hu">Feldolgozza és megjeleníti a ventilátor-sebesség napló adatait. Habár ez a plugin működik az összes platformon, a SpeedFan csak Windowson fut. Ezért ez a plugin elsősorban az Kodi-t Windowson futtató felhasználóknak készült. Annak érdekében, hogy az információkat megfelelően dolgozzuk fel, olvassa el a readme.txt fájlt, hogy SpeedFan naplót megfelelően beállíthassa.</description>
		<description lang="id">Membaca dan menampilkan informasi dari log SpeedFan. Meskipun plugin ini bisa berjalan di platform manapun, SpeedFan hanya dapat berjalan di Windows, jadi plugin ini dibangun seara optimal khusus untuk mereka yang menggunakan Kodi di WIndows. Silakan merujuk ke readme.txt untuk informasi mengenai bagaimana cara mengkonfigurasi log SpeedFan Anda supaya plugin bisa membacanya dengan baik.</description>
		<description lang="it">Analizza e mostra informazioni dal log. di SpeedFan. Mentre questo plug-in funziona su ogni piattaforma, SpeedFan funziona solo su Windows, quindi ottimizzato per persone che usano Kodi su Windows. Leggi il file readme.txt per le informazioni su come configurare il tuo SpeedFan log. così che il plug-in lo potrà analizzare correttamente.</description>
		<description lang="nl">Verzameld en laat informatie zien van het SpeedFan log. Deze plugin werkt op elk platform alleen werkt SpeedFan enkel op Windows en is daarom geoptimaliseerd voor mensen die Kodi gebruiken op Windows. Lees alstublieft readme.txt voor informatie hoe je het SpeedFan log in kunt stellen zodat de plugin correct de gegevens verzameld.</description>
		<description lang="pl">Analizuje i wyświetla informacje z dziennika SpeedFan. Wtyczka powinna działać na każdej platformie, jednakże SpeedFan optymalnie działa w systemie Windows, więc wskazane jest korzystanie z niej tylko na tej platformie. Proszę zapoznaj się z treścią pliku readme.txt, gdzie podane są informacje, jak skonfigurować dziennik SpeedFan tak, aby wtyczka mogła analizować prawidłowo.</description>
		<description lang="pt">Recolhe e exibe informação do log do Speedfan. Apesar deste plugin funcionar em qualquer plataforma, o Speedfan apenas funciona no Windows. Por favor verifique o readme.txt para obter informação sobre como configurar o seu log do Speedfan, para o plugin poder analisá-lo correctamente.</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Analisa e apresenta informações do registro SpeedFan. Embora este plugin funcione em qualquer plataforma, SpeedFan só funciona no Windows, então é optimizado para as pessoas que utilizam o Kodi no Windows. Por favor, veja o arquivo readme.txt para obter informações sobre como configurar o registro SpeedFan para que o plugin possa analisá-lo corretamente.</description>
		<description lang="ru">Извлекает и отображает информацию из журнала SpeedFan. Данный плагин работает на всех платформах, но сам SpeedFan есть только для Windows, поэтому данный плагин прежде всего пригодится пользователям Windows. Пожалуйста, ознакомьтесь с файлом readme.txt для более подробной информации о конфигурации SpeedFan и настройках лога, чтобы данный плагин смог правильно его распарсить.</description>
		<description lang="sk">Rozoberá a zobrazuje informácie zo SpeedFan logu. Síce tento doplnok funguje na všetkých platformách, SpeedFan funguje len na Windows, a preto je tento doplnok určený užívateľom Kodi na Windows. Prosím prečítajte readme.txt aby ste sa dozvedeli ako nastaviť SpeedFan log tak, aby ho tento doplnok vedel správne rozoberať.</description>
		<description lang="sv">Analyserar och visar information från SpeedFan loggen. Trots att detta tillägg fungerar på alla plattformar, fungerar SpeedFan endast på Windows, så det är optimerat för folk som använder Kodi på Windows. Läs readme.txt för mer information hur du konfigurerar din SpeedFan logg så att tillägget kan analysera det riktigt.</description>
		<description lang="zh">分析和显示从SpeedFan日志获取的信息。由于SpeedFan只有Windows版，因此本插件仅用于运行在Windows平台的Kodi。请阅读readme.txt中关于如何配置SpeedFan日志以使本插件能正确分析处理的相关说明。</description>
		<language></language>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
		<forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?p=1014479</forum>
		<website>http://wiki.xbmc.org/index.php?title=Add-on:SpeedFan_Information_Display</website>
		<email>speedfaninfo.xbmc@gmail.com</email>
		<source>https://github.com/pkscout/script.speedfaninfo</source>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.weatherstation.lite" name="Weather Station Lite" version="1.1.0~beta1" provider-name="pkscout">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0" />
		<import addon="xbmc.addon" version="17.0.0" />
		<import addon="script.module.kodi-six" version="0.0.3" />
		<import addon="script.module.future" version="0.16.0.4" />
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py">
		<provides>executable</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<news>
v.1.1.0
Python 2/3 compatability
		</news>
		<description lang="en">Reads weather data from external sources and adds that information to the weather window properties.</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">Reads weather data from from external sources and adds that information to the weather window properties.</description>
		<description lang="en_US">Reads weather data from from external sources and adds that information to the weather window properties.</description>
		<language></language>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 3, 29 June 2007</license>
		<forum></forum>
		<website></website>
		<email></email>
		<source>https://github.com/pkscout/script.weatherstation</source>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.whereareyou" name="Where Are You" provider-name="pkscout" version="0.1.1">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.26.0" />
		<import addon="xbmc.addon" version="17.9.910" />
		<import addon="script.module.kodi-six" version="0.0.3" />
        <import addon="script.module.future" version="0.16.0.4" />
	</requires>
	<extension library="default.py" point="xbmc.python.script">
		<provides>executable</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<news>
v.0.1.1
- Python 2/3 compatibility
		</news>
		<summary lang="en_GB">Hacky module to display a custom dialog box when playing external media.</summary>
		<description lang="en_GB">Where Are You is a hacky module for Kodi that accepts a URL from a stream file and then displays a dialog box with the title and message from the stream file URL.  After the dialog is dismissed a black video plays for 2 seconds.  This is basically to do what the media stub file *should* do, which is display a title and a message for a given file, but the media stub only works if you have an optical drive attached to the device running Kodi.
</description>
		<language />
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
		<source>https://github.com/pkscout/plugin.whereareyou</source>
	</extension>
</addon>

</addons>
